[{"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/皮鼓.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/魔方.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/音响.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/书本_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_2.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/鱼缸.svg", "type": "orb"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 2], [2, 1], [3, 3], [4, 3], [5, 1], [6, 0]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/鱼缸.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/筛子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/铅笔_2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/冰箱.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/保险箱.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/魔方.svg", "type": "cube"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 1], [2, 2], [3, 3], [4, 3], [5, 0], [6, 1]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/柜子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/棒球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/筛子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/时钟.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/冰箱.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/手电筒_1.svg", "type": "cylinder"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 3], [1, 0], [2, 0], [3, 1], [4, 1], [5, 3], [6, 2]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/筛子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/冰箱.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/鱼缸.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_3.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/日历.svg", "type": "cuboid"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 3], [2, 0], [3, 0], [4, 2], [5, 1], [6, 3]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/日历.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/时钟.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/皮鼓.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/门.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_2.svg", "type": "cube"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 3], [1, 1], [2, 0], [3, 2], [4, 0], [5, 3], [6, 1]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/油笔棒.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_1.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/微波炉.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/书本_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 2], [1, 1], [2, 0], [3, 3], [4, 3], [5, 0], [6, 1]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/魔方.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/手机.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_3.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_2.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg", "type": "orb"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 1], [2, 3], [3, 1], [4, 3], [5, 2], [6, 0]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/字母.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_2.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/筛子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/柜子_2.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/汽水瓶.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/鱼缸.svg", "type": "orb"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 0], [2, 3], [3, 1], [4, 3], [5, 2], [6, 0]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/微波炉.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/铅笔_2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_2.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/字母.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/鱼缸.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/音响.svg", "type": "cuboid"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 3], [2, 2], [3, 1], [4, 1], [5, 0], [6, 3]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_3.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/手电筒_1.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/日历.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/排球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/魔方.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/门.svg", "type": "cuboid"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 0], [4, 0], [5, 1], [6, 3]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/书本_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/日历.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_2.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/排球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/时钟.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/饮料瓶.svg", "type": "cylinder"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 3], [1, 3], [2, 1], [3, 0], [4, 1], [5, 0], [6, 2]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/皮箱 .svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/筛子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_2.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_1.svg", "type": "cylinder"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 3], [1, 1], [2, 0], [3, 1], [4, 3], [5, 0], [6, 2]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/书本_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/棒球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/菜篮子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_1.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/微波炉.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/排球.svg", "type": "orb"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 3], [1, 2], [2, 0], [3, 1], [4, 1], [5, 3], [6, 0]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/书本_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/铅笔_1.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/鱼缸.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/字母.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_1.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_2.svg", "type": "cuboid"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 3], [1, 2], [2, 0], [3, 0], [4, 1], [5, 1], [6, 3]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/饼干盒.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/菜篮子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_3.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_2.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 3], [2, 1], [3, 1], [4, 3], [5, 0], [6, 2]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/胶水.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/书本_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/柜子_2.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_1.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 3], [4, 0], [5, 1], [6, 1]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/棒球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/排球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/手电筒_1.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/皮箱 .svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/筛子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/冰箱.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 0], [2, 2], [3, 3], [4, 1], [5, 3], [6, 1]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}, {"body": [{"stem": "找朋友。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/棒球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/手机.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/柜子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/皮鼓.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/时钟.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/魔方.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg", "type": "orb"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 3], [2, 3], [3, 2], [4, 1], [5, 1], [6, 0]], "knowledges": ["认识立体图形"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-5-01"}]